RG 014, Department of Banking
Connecticut State Library
- Series 1. Receivership Files, 1918-1971; 92.5 cubic feet
  - Legislation, circa 1940-1971; 12 cubic feet
    - State Banks and Trust Companies, Bills Not Passed, 1971 (Box 28)
    - Truth-In-Lending, Bills Not Passed (Box 28)
    - Uniform Consumer Credit Code Legislation, Not Passed (Box 28)
    - Credit Unions, 1971 Bills Passed (Box 28)
    - Savings Banks, 1971 Bills Passed (Box 28)
    - Securities Legislation, 1971 Bills Passed (Box 28)
    - Small Loan, Sales Finance, 1971 Bills Passed (Box 28)
    - State Banks and Trust Companies, 1971 Bills Passed (Box 28)
    - Truth-In-Lending, 1971 Bills Passed (Box 28)
    - Miscellaneous, 1971 Bills Passed (Box 28)
    - Building and Loan Associations, Bills Not Passed, 1971 (Box 28)
    - Credit Unions, Bills Not Passed (Box 28)
    - Debt Adjusters, Sales Finance, Small Loans, Bills Not Passed (Box 28)
    - 1971, Bills Being Submitted By Banking Department (Box 28)
    - Interlocking Directors (1965 Legislation) (Box 28)
    - 1971 Legislation File (Box 28)
    - 1971 Credit Union Legislation (Box 28)
    - 1971 Savings Bank Legislation (Box 28)
    - 1971 Securities Legislation (Box 28)
    - 1971 State Bank and Trust Company Legislation (Box 28)
    - Legislation, Uniform Consumer Credit Code (Box 28)
    - Building and Loan Associations, 1971 Bills Passed (Box 28)
    - 1957 Session of the Legislature (Box 28A)
    - 1953 and 1955 Regular and Special Sessions of State Legislature (Box 28A)
    - Legislative Record, General Assembly, 1949 (Box 28A)
    - General Assembly, Legislative Record, 1951 (Box 28A)
    - 1959, Legislative Material (Box 28A)
    - 1957 and 1959 Banking Department Memoranda on Bills Presented (Box 28A)
    - 1959 Bills Vetoed By the Governor, S.B. 567, H.B. 3315 (Box 28A)
    - 1959 House and Senate Bills Not Passed (Box 28A)
    - 1959, Legislative Proposals (Box 28A)
    - Departmental Regulations, 1959 Session (Box 28A)
    - Savings Bank Life Insurance, 1963 Legislation (Box 29)
    - Uniform Commercial Code, 1963 (Box 29)
    - Extra Engrossed Copies, Special Acts (Box 29)
    - Extra Engrossed Copies, Public Acts (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous Legislation, 1963 (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 29)
    - Building or Savings & Loan Associations (Box 29)
    - Commercial Banks (Box 29)
    - Credit Unions (Box 29)
    - Savings Banks (Box 29)
    - Small Loan Legislation, 1963 (Box 29)
    - 1963 Legislation File, Miscellaneous (Box 29)
    - Uniform Commercial Code, 1963 Legislation (Box 29)
    - 1963 Final Legislative Index (Box 29)
    - Commercial Bank Legislation, 1963 (Box 29)
    - Credit Union Legislation, 1963 (Box 29)
    - Sales Finance Legislation, 1963 (Box 29)
    - Savings and Loan Legislation, 1963 (Box 29)
    - Savings Bank Legislation, 1963 (Box 29)
    - Securities Legislation, 1963 (Vetoed) (Box 29)
    - 1963 Preliminary Manual of the General Assembly (Box 29)
    - 1963 Legislative Record (Box 29)
    - 1963 Banking Department Memoranda on Bills Presented (Box 29)
    - Commercial Bank Legislation, 1963 (Box 29)
    - Credit Union Legislation, 1963 (Box 29)
    - 1963 Savings and Loan Legislation (Box 29)
    - Savings Bank Life Insurance Legislation, 1963 (Box 29)
    - Savings Bank Legislation, 1963 (Box 29)
    - 1961 Banking Department Memoranda on Bills Presented (Box 30)
    - 1961 Final Legislative Index (Box 30)
    - Material Re: Escheating savings accounts under $5 to State within less than 10 years (Box 30)
    - Building or Savings and Loan Associations, 1961 Legislation (Box 30)
    - Credit Unions, 1961 Legislation (Box 30)
    - Money Forwarders, 1961 Legislation (Box 30)
    - Private Bankers, 1961 Legislation (Box 30)
    - Sales Finance Companies, 1961 Legislation (Box 30)
    - Extra Engrossed Copies (Box 30)
    - Laws of General Interest, 1961 Legislation (Box 30)
    - Savings Banks and/or Savings Departments, 1961 Legislation (Box 30)
    - State Banks and Trust Companies, 1961 Legislation (Box 30)
    - HB-3602, Uniform Commercial Code, 1961 (Box 30)
    - 1961 Preliminary Manual of the General Assembly (Box 30)
    - 1961 Legislative Record (Box 30)
    - 1959 Legislative Record (Box 30)
    - Extra Engrossed Copies (Box 30)
    - 1961 House and Senate Bills Not Passed (Box 30)
    - Small Loan Legislation, 1961 (Box 30)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 30)
    - Commercial Banks (Box 30)
    - Credit Unions (Box 30)
    - Private Banks (Box 30)
    - Savings Banks (Box 30)
    - Savings Banks" Railroad Investment Committee (Box 30)
    - Savings and Loan Material (Box 30)
    - Securities, Small Loan & Sales Finance (Box 30)
    - 1967 Legislative File (Box 31)
    - Proposed Legislation (Box 31)
    - 1967 Preliminary Manual of the General Assembly (Box 31)
    - 1967 Legislative File, Miscellaneous (Box 31)
    - 1967 Credit Union Legislation (Box 31)
    - 1967 Miscellaneous Legislation, Not Passed (Box 31)
    - 1967 Savings and Loan Legislation (Box 31)
    - 1967 Savings Bank Legislation (Box 31)
    - Repeal of Segregation of Savings Departments (Box 31)
    - 1967 Savings Bank Life Insurance Company Legislation (Box 31)
    - 1967 Securities Legislation (Box 31)
    - State Bank and Trust Company Legislation, 1967 (Box 31)
    - 1967 Trust Department Legislation (Box 31)
    - 1967 Building or Savings and Loan Legislation, Not Passed (Box 31)
    - 1967 Credit Union Legislation, Not Passed (Box 31)
    - 1967 Savings Bank Legislation, Not Passed (Box 31)
    - 1967 Savings Bank Life Insurance Legislation, Not Passed (Box 31)
    - 1967 Securities, Sales Finance, Small Loan Legislation, Not Passed (Box 31)
    - 1967 State Bank and Trust Company Legislation, Not Passed (Box 31)
    - Extra Engrossed Copies (Box 31)
    - Extra Engrossed Copies, Special Acts, 1967 (Box 31)
    - Savings Bank Legislation (Passed By 1967 Legislature) (Box 31)
    - Building or Savings & Loan Legislation (Passed By 1967 Legislature) (Box 31)
    - Securities and Sales Finance Legislation (Passed By 1967 Legislature) (Box 31)
    - Credit Union Legislation (Passed By 1967 Legislature) (Box 31)
    - State Bank and Trust Company Legislation (Passed By 1967 Legislature) (Box 31)
    - Miscellaneous Bills Passed By 1967 General Assembly (Box 31)
    - Laws of General Interest (Passed By 1967 Legislature) (Box 31)
    - Corrected copy of 1967 Law Book (Box 31)
    - 1967 Legislative index (Box 31)
    - Extra Engrossed Copies (Box 31)
    - 1967 Legislative Memorandums (Box 32)
    - 1965 Legislative Memoranda (Box 32)
    - Extra Engrossed Copies (Box 32)
    - Miscellaneous Copies (Box 32)
    - 1965 Final Legislative Index (Box 32)
    - Banking Department Legislation (Box 32)
    - 1965 Legislative File, Miscellaneous (Box 32)
    - 1965, Commercial Bank Legislation (Box 32)
    - Credit Union Legislation (Box 32)
    - 1965 Savings and Loan Legislation (Box 32)
    - 1965, Savings Bank Legislation (Box 32)
    - Proposed Changes, Sec. 36-139, Dividends (Box 32)
    - Building or Savings & Loan Legislation (Passed By 1965 Legislature) (Box 32)
    - Commercial Bank Legislation, 1965 (Passed By 1965 Legislature) (Box 32)
    - Credit Union Legislation, 1965 (Passed By 1965 Legislature) (Box 32)
    - Private Bankers, 1965 Legislation (Box 32)
    - Savings Bank Legislation, 1965 (Passed By 1965 Legislature) (Box 32)
    - Securities, 1965 (Box 32)
    - Laws of General Interest, 1965 (Box 32)
    - Miscellaneous Bills Passed During 1965 Session of General Assembly (Box 32)
    - 1965 Legislative Record (Box 32)
    - Building or Savings and Loan Association, 1965 Legislation (Not Passed) (Box 32)
    - Credit Unions, 1965 Legislation (Not Passed) (Box 32)
    - Savings Banks and Savings Departments, 1965 Legislation (Not Passed) (Box 32)
    - Securities and Sales Finance, 1965 Legislation (Not Passed) (Box 32)
    - State Banks and Trust Companies, 1965 Legislation (Not Passed) (Box 32)
    - 1965 Miscellaneous Legislation (Not Passed) (Box 32)
    - Untitled folder (Box 32)
    - Corrected copy of Law Book, 1969 (Box 32)
    - Consumer Credit Code (Box 32)
    - 1969 Legislative File, Miscellaneous (Box 32)
    - Preliminary Manual of the General Assembly, 1969 (Box 32)
    - 1969 Credit Union Legislation (Box 32)
    - 1969 Savings and Loan Legislation (Box 32)
    - Building or Savings and Loan Legislation (Passed By 1969 Legislature) (Box 32)
    - Preliminary Manual of the General Assembly, 1971 (Box 33)
    - My copy of Law Book with corrections for 1971 (Box 33)
    - My copy of proof (Box 33)
    - Extra Engrossed Copies (Box 33)
    - Special Acts (Box 33)
    - 1969 Small Loan Legislation (Box 33)
    - 1969 Building or Savings and Loan Bills, Not Passed (Box 33)
    - 1969 Connecticut Securities Act Bills, Not Passed (Box 33)
    - 1969 Credit Union Bills, Not Passed (Box 33)
    - 1969 Sales Finance and Small Loan Bills, Not Passed (Box 33)
    - 1969 Savings Bank Bills, Not Passed (Box 33)
    - 1969 State Bank and Trust Company Legislation, Not Passed (Box 33)
    - 1969 Truth-in-Lending Legislation, Not Passed (Box 33)
    - 1969 Miscellaneous Legislation, Not Passed (Box 33)
    - 1969 State Bank and Trust Company Legislation (Box 33)
    - Untitled folder (Box 33)
    - 1969 Legislative Record (Box 33)
    - Special Acts (Box 33)
    - Legislative Memorandum for Use of Bank Examiners (Box 33)
      - House Bills (Box 33)
      - Senate Bills (Box 33)
    - 1969 Legislative Memorandums (Box 33)
    - Credit Union Legislation (Passed By 1969 Legislature) (Box 33)
    - Savings Bank Legislation (Passed By 1969 Legislature) (Box 33)
    - Securities, Small Loan & Sales Finance Legislation (Passed By 1969 Legislature) (Box 33)
    - Miscellaneous Legislation (Passed By 1969 Legislature) (Box 33)
    - State Bank and Trust Company Legislation (Passed By 1969 Legislature) (Box 33)
    - Truth-in-Lending Legislation (Passed By 1969 Legislature) (Box 33)
    - 1969 Savings Bank Legislation (Box 33)
    - Asian Development Bank (Box 33)
    - 1969 Securities Legislation (Box 33)
  - Pension Plans, circa 1940-1970; 2 cubic feet
    - City Savings Bank, Meriden (Box 36)
    - Retirement Plan, Connecticut Savings Bank of New Haven, Employees" Retirement Plan (Box 36)
    - People's Savings Bank, Bridgeport, Pension Plan (Box 36)
    - Putnam Savings Bank (Box 36)
    - Savings Bank of Danbury (Box 36)
    - Unarranged material, 3 inches (Box 36)
    - Savings Bank of Manchester, Pension Plan (Box 36)
      - New Haven Savings Bank, Retirement Plan (Box 36)
    - Savings Bank of New Britain, Retirement Plan (Box 36)
    - Society for Savings Pension Plan (Box 36)
    - Stamford Savings Bank, Pension Plan (Box 36)
    - Waterbury Savings Bank, Employees" Retirement Plan (Box 36)
    - Woodbury Savings Bank, Trusteed Pension Plan (Box 36)
    - MacDonald, Bristol Savings Bank, Connecticut General, Supplemental Plans, Thomaston (Box 36)
    - MacDonald, Connecticut Mutual Pension Plan (Box 36)
    - Southington Savings and Loan Association, Pension Plan (Box 36)
    - Retirement Fund of the Federal Home Loan Bank System (Box 36)
    - Savings & Loan Associations, Pension Plan, Connecticut General Life (Box 36)
    - Insurance (Box 36)
    - Savings Banks, Pensions, Aetna Life Annuity and Group Insurance Plan (Box 37)
    - Brooklyn Savings Bank, Danielson (Box 37)
    - Chelsea Savings Bank, Norwich (Box 37)
    - Chester Savings Bank (Box 37)
    - City Savings Bank, Bridgeport (Box 37)
    - Collinsville Savings Society (Box 37)
    - Deep River Savings Bank (Box 37)
    - Dime Savings Bank, Hartford (Box 37)
    - Dime Savings Bank, Norwich (Box 37)
    - Guilford Savings Bank (Box 37)
    - Jewett City Savings Bank (Box 37)
    - Mechanics & Farmers Savings Bank, Bridgeport (Box 37)
    - Meriden Savings Bank (Box 37)
    - National Savings Bank, New Haven (Box 37)
    - Naugatuck Savings Bank (Box 37)
    - New Haven Savings Bank (Box 37)
    - Norwich Savings Society (Box 37)
    - Savings Bank of Ansonia (Box 37)
    - Savings Bank of New London (Box 37)
    - Savings Bank of Tolland (Box 37)
    - Savings Banks" Association of Connecticut (Box 37)
    - Savings Banks" Deposit Guaranty Fund of Connecticut, Inc. (Box 37)
    - Society for Savings, Hartford (Box 37)
    - South Norwalk Savings Bank (Box 37)
    - Southington Savings Bank (Box 37)
    - Stafford Savings Bank, Stafford Springs (Box 37)
    - State Savings Bank, Hartford (Box 37)
    - Thomaston Savings Bank (Box 37)
    - Torrington Savings Bank (Box 37)
    - Winsted Savings Bank (Box 37)
    - Woodbury Savings Bank (Box 37)
  - Trustees under Mortgage, 1938-1950; 1 cubic foot
    - Ardolino, Antonio, Trustee (West Haven) (Box 38)
    - Bridgeport, City Trust Company (Box 38)
    - Capuano, Ralph J., Trustee (New Haven) (Box 38)
    - Carter, L. Russell and Earle B. Carter, Trustees (Waterbury) (Box 38)
    - Dana, J. Dwight, Trustee (New Haven) (Box 38)
    - Dejon, J. Peter, Trustee (New Haven) (Box 38)
    - Drazen, Harry, Trustee (New Haven) (Box 38)
    - First National Bank and Trust Company, New Haven, Trustee (Correspondence) (Box 38)
    - First National Bank and Trust Company, New Haven, Trustee (Mortgages) (Box 38)
    - First National Bank and Trust Company, New Haven, Trustee (Real Estate) (Box 38)
    - Ford, Edwards D., Trustee (Philadelphia, Pa.) (Box 38)
    - Francis, F. Anthony, Trustee, Hartford, Conn. (Box 38)
    - Gabriel, Leon M., Trustee (West Haven) (Box 38)
    - Hart, Arnold R., Trustee (Stratford) (Box 38)
    - Hartford-Connecticut Trust Company, Trustee (Correspondence) (Box 38)
    - Hartford-Connecticut Trust Company, Trustee (Mortgages) (Box 38)
    - Hartford-Connecticut Trust Company, Trustee (Real Estate) (Box 38)
    - Hartford National Bank and Trust Company, Trustee (Correspondence) (Box 38)
    - Hartford National Bank and Trust Company, Trustee (Mortgages) (Box 38)
    - Hartford National Bank and Trust Company, Trustee (Real Estate) (Box 38)
    - Kahn, Elliott M. and Ralph T. Heymsfeld, Trustees (New Your City) (Box 38)
    - Kirby, Bertha E., New Haven (Box 38)
    - Korn, David S., Trustee (New Haven) (Box 38)
    - Leddy, Frank A., Trustee (New Haven) (Box 38)
    - McKeon, James M., Trustee (Stamford) (Box 38)
    - Mendel, Lillian, Trustee (c/o Nelson Harris, Attorney, 42 Church St., New Haven) (Box 38)
    - Meriden Trust & Safe Deposit Company, Trustee (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Section 784d - Trust Mortgages) (Box 38)
    - Morris, Emanuel J., Trustee (New Haven) (Box 38)
    - Morris, Regina, Trustee (42 Sumac Avenue, West Haven) (Box 38)
    - New Haven Bank, N.B.A., Trustee (Correspondence) (Box 38)
    - New Haven Bank, N.B.A., Trustee (Mortgages) (Box 38)
    - New Haven Bank, N.B.A., Trustee (Real Estate) (Box 38)
    - Phoenix State Bank and Trust Company, Hartford, Trustee (Correspondence) (Box 38)
    - Phoenix State Bank and Trust Company, Hartford, Trustee (Mortgages) (Box 38)
    - Phoenix State Bank and Trust Company, Hartford, Trustee (Real Estate) (Box 38)
    - Rubin, Louis, Trustee (New Haven) (Box 38)
    - Schaub, F. C., Trustee (Philadelphia, Pa.) (Box 38)
    - Schwartz, Minnie and Lena S. Windt, Trustees (Box 38)
    - The Second National Bank, New Haven, Trustee (Box 38)
    - Shepard, Lulu M., Trustee (New Haven) (Box 38)
    - Stamford Trust Company, Trustee (Box 38)
    - Thomson, W. A., New Haven (Box 38)
    - Union and New Haven Trust Company, New Haven, Trustee (Correspondence) (Box 38)
    - Union and New Haven Trust Company, New Haven, Trustee (Mortgages) (Box 38)
    - Union and New Haven Trust Company, New Haven, Trustee (Real Estate) (Box 38)
    - United Bank and Trust Company, Hartford, Trustee (Box 38)
    - Hickey, Levi P. M., Trustee (Hartford) Trusteeship Terminated, See Levi Hickey's Letter Dated 9-27-50 (Enclosed Herein) (Box 38)
  - Insurance Policies, circa 1940-1949; 2 cubic feet
    - Records (Box 39-40)
  - Closed and Merged Banks, circa 1940-1969; 1 cubic foot
    - Connecticut Fiduciaries" Fund, Inc., 1966; 2 folders (Box 41)
    - Connecticut Mortgage & Title Guaranty Company, New Haven (Box 41)
    - Connecticut River Banking Company, Hartford, 1947 (Box 41)
    - County Bank and Trust Company of Danielson, 1967 (Box 41)
    - Danielson Building and Loan Association (Box 41)
    - Danielson Trust Company, 2 folders (Box 41)
    - Deep River National Bank (Box 41)
    - D"esopo (P.M.) Company, Hartford (Box 41)
    - Devon Bank & Trust Company (Box 41)
    - Dime Savings Bank, Waterbury (Box 41)
    - East Hampton Building and Loan Association, 1955 (Box 41)
      - General Correspondence (Box 41)
      - Directors" Acknowledgment (Box 41)
      - By-Laws (Box 41)
      - Charter (Box 41)
    - East Hampton Bank & Trust Company (Box 41)
    - East Hartford Building & Loan Association (Box 41)
    - East Hartford Trust Company, 1945-1950; 2 folders (Box 41)
    - East Haven Bank & Trust Company (Box 41)
    - Ellithorpe, Ira V. and Horace T. Burgess, New Haven, 2 folders (Box 41)
    - Elm City Savings and Loan Association, New Haven, 1950-1957 (Box 41)
      - General Correspondence (Box 41)
      - By-Laws (Box 41)
      - Charter (Box 41)
    - Fairfield County Trust Company, Stamford, 1969 (Box 41)
    - Fairfield County Bank & Trust Company, Norwalk (Box 41)
    - Fairfield Trust Company (Box 41)
    - Fairfield Savings and Loan Association, 1955 (Box 41)
      - Directors" Acknowledgment (Box 41)
      - General Correspondence (Box 41)
      - By-Laws (Box 41)
      - Charter (Box 41)
    - Federal Building and Loan Association, Bridgeport (Box 41)
      - Charter (Box 41)
      - By-Laws (Box 41)
    - Portland Building & Loan Association, 1964-1966, 1969 (Box 41)
  - Bank records, circa 1918-1967; 45 cubic feet
    - American Bank and Trust Company, Bridgeport (Box 42)
      - Savings accounts (Box 42)
      - Motions filed, 1933 September - 1936 January (Box 42)
      - Motions filed at Superior Court (Box 42)
      - Miscellaneous Trust material including probate certificates, assignments (Box 43)
      - Recapitulation of Receiver's Return of Claims (Box 44)
      - Legal papers (Box 44)
        - Applications (Box 44)
        - Court orders - receivership termination, etc. (Box 44)
        - Real estate transactions (Box 44)
      - Legal papers (Box 45)
        - Real estate transactions (Box 45)
        - Miscellaneous checks paid out through the bank commissioner to bank clientele, 1947 (Box 45)
      - Court orders (Box 46)
        - Real estate sold, 1937-1944 (Box 46)
        - Release of mortgage, 1936-1967 (Box 46)
      - Commercial Bank and Trust: mortgages, deeds, miscellaneous ledger cards, (pre-receivership period) (Box 47)
      - Mortgages (Box 48)
    - Broadway Bank and Trust, New Haven (Box 49)
      - Legal papers including receivership termination, 1951 (Box 49)
      - Compromise settlements closed, 1935-1944 (Box 49)
      - Foreclosures, 1935-1940 (Box 49)
      - Real estate sold, 1936-1947 (Box 49)
      - Reports, 1936-1951 (Box 49)
      - Miscellaneous court orders (Box 49)
      - Receiver's check register, 1936-1951 (Box 49)
      - Trust agreements, securities, 1930-1935 (Box 50)
      - Checks, 1929-1930 (Box 50)
      - Miscellaneous probate material (Box 51)
      - Correspondence, 1918-1959 (Box 51)
      - Release of mortgage, 1935-1955 (Box 51)
    - Citizens Bank and Trust, New Haven (Box 51)
      - Legal papers, 1936-1951 (Box 51)
        - Applications (Box 51)
        - Release of mortgage (Box 51)
      - Compromise settlements closed, 1935-1947 (Box 51)
      - Reports, miscellaneous (Box 51)
      - Court orders, 1935-1951 (Box 52)
    - Windsor Locks Bank and Trust Company (Box 52)
      - Folder containing checks and correspondence concerning payment of liquidation dividend (Box 52)
      - Stock ledger (Box 52)
      - Federal income tax returns, 1936-1943 (Box 52)
      - Record of taxes paid (Box 52)
      - Salary list, 1932-1935 (Box 52)
    - City Bank and Trust Company, Hartford (Box 52)
      - Legal papers, real estate sold, 1937 November - 1940 August (Box 52)
      - Compromise claims, 1940-1943 (Box 53)
      - Applications for sale of real estate, 1940-1944 (Box 53)
      - Trust agreements (Box 53)
      - Book III, Director's record, 1926 December 29 - 1930 January 8 (Box 54)
      - General ledger, Savings Department, 1932-1944 (Box 54)
      - Legal papers (Box 54)
        - Compromise settlements closed (Box 54)
        - Real estate sold (Box 54)
      - Miscellaneous trust material (Box 55)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 55)
      - Correspondence, Before 1931 (Box 56)
      - Legal papers, 1932-1944 (Box 56)
        - Compromise settlements closed (Box 56)
        - Release of mortgage, 1936-1962 (Box 56)
        - Releases made out for sale of assets, 1944 (Box 56)
        - Other legal papers (Box 56)
      - Receiver's check register, 1939-1950 (Box 57)
      - Correspondence (Box 57)
      - Legal papers (Box 57)
        - Receivership judgment, 1935 October (Box 57)
        - Reports (Box 57)
        - Miscellaneous, 1936-1941 (Box 57)
      - City Bank and Trust Co., in receivership (Box 57)
      - Inventory and appraisal (Box 57)
    - Commercial Trust Company, New Britain (Box 58)
      - Industrial certificates of deposit, 1920-1930; 3 volumes (Box 58)
      - Papers regarding property in Rocky Hill, Conn. (Box 58)
      - Recapitulation of Receiver's Return of Claims (Box 58)
      - Court orders, 1935-1949 (Box 59)
      - Correspondence and papers, 1918-1962 (Box 59)
      - Legal papers (Box 60)
        - Release of mortgage (Box 60)
        - Compromise of settlements closed (Box 60)
        - Foreclosures (Box 60)
        - Reports (Box 60)
        - Receivership termination (Box 60)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 60)
      - Receiver's check register (Box 60)
      - Real estate files (Box 61)
      - Miscellaneous legal papers (Box 61)
      - Dividend receipts, 1943-1945 (Box 62)
      - Miscellaneous receipts (Box 62)
      - Miscellaneous checks (Box 62)
      - Legal files, 1930-1934 (Box 63)
      - Mortgages (Box 64)
      - Ledger cards (Box 64)
      - Stock ledger (Box 64)
    - Hartford Jewish Credit Union (Box 65)
      - Judgment, Richard Rapport, bank commissioner v. The Hartford Jewish Credit Union, with forged notes, 1951 March 22; 2 folders (Box 65)
      - Bank statements and cancelled checks (Box 65)
      - Records of the board of directors, minutes, and the credit committee applications for membership (Box 65)
      - Letters (Box 65)
    - Mechanics Bank, New Haven (Box 66)
      - R.F.C. ledger cards, 1932-1934 (Box 66)
      - Alphabetized court orders from "M", 1932-1934 (Box 66)
      - Legal papers (Box 67)
        - Real estate sold (Box 67)
        - Foreclosures, 1923-1945 (Box 67)
        - Receivership termination (Box 67)
        - Receiver's check register (Box 67)
        - Court orders, 1932-1951 (Box 68)
        - Application concerning sale of assets (Box 68)
        - Reports (Box 68)
        - Compromise settlements closed, 1935-1944 (Box 69)
      - Court orders, 1933-1944 (Box 70)
      - Court orders, 1936-1939 (Box 71)
      - Recapitulation of Receiver's Return of Claims, 1933 February 15; 2 copies (Box 71)
      - Mortgages and miscellaneous trust material (Box 72)
      - Summary statement, 1932 October 31 (Box 72)
      - List of holdings - memorandum (Box 73)
      - Trust Department file (Box 73)
      - Correspondence and papers, 1918-1935, 1954-1961 (Box 73)
      - Clara Mires and Alexander Eftimes (Box 73)
    - Merchants Trust Company, Waterbury (Box 73)
      - Receiver's check register (Box 73)
      - Legal papers (Box 73)
        - Termination of receivership (Box 73)
        - Compromise settlements closed (Box 73)